keeping track of tasks across different
projects and teams can be tricky
especially when clients are using
different tools but don't worry FN birs
is here to simplify things for you and
your clients its built-in webook feature
allows you and your clients to create
tasks via incoming webbook across
platforms and turn your project
management into a more efficient and
effective workflow let's kick off with
lber settings to see how it works right
away you will find incoming web hooks
select it and click the ADD web hook
button to create a new one provide your
web hook name choose the board select
the stage and finalize by hitting create
next copy the WB hook URL you want to
send your post request to besides you
have all the keys to map fields and
options to link CRM contacts by ID email
first name or last name let's update it
for now need to make changes later the
edit button is always there for you you
can copy any information customize your
Web book or delete it easily whenever
you like all right the Web book is all
set and time to see it in action for
example I'll use Postman as the source
system and your project board as the
destination as I'm already logged in the
rest becomes way easier for me first
change the method from get to post since
post requests are designed to send data
to a server for creating or updating a
resource next paste the wave hook URL
into the post field ensure you provide
the tile key as it is essential for the
wave hook to function then add any other
necessary Keys based on your
requirements and click the send button
to create the task now if you get back
to FL words you will see the task has
been added to the defined word and Stage
just like that you can also add labels
set dates and assign it using incoming
web hook that's how fnirs allows you to
work across platform firms keep your
project boards updated and convert
project management barriers into
breakthroughs to experience the seamless
efficiency you have been searching for
while managing any project get flend
Birds now
[Music]